Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - G
        - Gaston - We come to take control, 1981; SR-14425; Gaston (Box 276)
          Chocolate Cholly's
          Gastonia, North Carolina
        - Gaston - We come to take control, 1981; SR-14426; Gaston (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14425. Different discs.
        - GA.T. - Smiling faces sometimes, 1995; SR-14427; GA.T. (Box 276)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3218; A-side Matrix # MCA 12171 FDS-1
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - GA.T. - Smiling faces sometimes, 1995; SR-14428; GA.T. (Box 276)
        - GA.T. - Smiling faces sometimes, 1995; SR-14429; GA.T. (Box 276)
        - Gathering All Of The Stars - We are the wild (remixes), 2002; SR-14430; Gathering All Of The Stars (Box 276)
          Catalog # SSJX 70005; A-side Matrix # S-48378 SSJX 70004 A
          DigiCube
          Japan
        - Gatling, Tommy - Help, 1989; SR-14431; Gatling, Tommy (Box 276)
          Catalog # TBLP 26000; A-side Matrix # TBLP-26000-A-SR 1
          Tommy Boy
        - Gatling, Tommy - Rock me good, 1990; SR-14432; Gatling, Tommy (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14433. Multiple copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # TB 938; A-side Matrix # TB-938 A
        - Gatling, Tommy - Rock me good, 1990; SR-14433; Gatling, Tommy (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14432. Multiple copies. Annotated.
        - Gaturs - Wasted, 1994; SR-14434; Gaturs; Willie Tee (Box 276)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0001; A-side Matrix # DEL LP 0001-A
          Funky Delicacies
        - Gaye, Marvin - Sanctified Lady, 1985; SR-14435; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # 44-05188; A-side Matrix # XSS-173395-2A
        - Gaye, Marvin - Piece of clay, 1996; SR-14436; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8343; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8343-A-SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Gaye, Marvin - Live at the London Palladium (Disc one), 1997; SR-14437; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14438. Double album.
          Catalog # 5259ML2; A-side Matrix # 5259ML2-A-1SA
          Tamla
        - Gaye, Marvin - Live at the London Palladium (Disc two), 1997; SR-14438; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14437. Double album.
        - Gaye, Marvin - In our liftime, 1981; SR-14439; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # T8-374M1; A-side Matrix # T8-374-M1-(A-15A)ZXJ
        - Gaye, Marvin - A musical testament 1964-1984 (Disc one), 1988; SR-14440; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14441. Double album.
          Catalog # 6255ML2; A-side Matrix # 6255ML2-A-15B XXJ
          Motown
        - Gaye, Marvin - A musical testament 1964-1984 (Disc two), 1988; SR-14441; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14440. Double album.
          Catalog # 6255ML2; A-side Matrix # 6255ML2-C-15B XXJ
        - Gaye, Marvin - Midnight love, 1982; SR-14442; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # CBS 85977; A-side Matrix # CBS 85977 A1
          CBS
        - Gaye, Marvin - Live in concert, 1999; SR-14443; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # DF 9904; A-side Matrix # DF 9904-A
          Dancefloor
        - Gaye, Marvin - Motown's greatest hits, 1992; SR-14444; Gaye, Marvin (Box 276)
          Catalog # 530 012-1; A-side Matrix # 530 012 1
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Tease me, 1982; SR-14445; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # DMD 369; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-43613-1
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Survive mix, 1980; SR-14446; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14447. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # Disco Mixer 510; A-side Matrix # 540
          Disco Mixer
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Survive mix, 1980; SR-14447; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14446. Multiple copies.
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Anybody wanna party?, 1978; SR-14448; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14449. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PD D 507; A-side Matrix # K-10519
          Polydor
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Anybody wanna party?, 1978; SR-14449; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14448. Multiple copies.
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Experience, 1975; SR-14450; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # M3G 4997; A-side Matrix # M3G4997AS-PRC-5
          MGM Records
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I am what I am, 1983; SR-14451; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04295; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04295-4 AB
          Silver Blue Records
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Love is just a heartbeat away, 1979; SR-14452; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # L33-1847; A-side Matrix # MCA 1985 W1
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Let me know (I have a right), 1979; SR-14453; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # PRO 111; A-side Matrix # PRO-11179NP4485-S-LONG-RE-CP1
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Just keep thinking about you (Disc one), 2001; SR-14454; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14455. Double album.
          Catalog # LGDJ-81359-1; A-side Matrix # 74321-81359-1A
          Logic Records
        - Gaynor, Gloria - Just keep thinking about you (Disc two), 2001; SR-14455; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14454. Double album.
          Catalog # LGDJ-81359-1; A-side Matrix # 74321-81359-1C
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I have a right, 1979; SR-14456; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 276)
          Catalog # PD-1-6231; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6231-AS-K
        - Gaznevada - Special agent man, 1983; SR-14457; Gaznevada (Box 276)
          Catalog # EXIT M 515; A-side Matrix # MEXITM515A
          Italian Records
        - G. B. Experience - Disco extravaganza, 1978; SR-14458; G. B. Experience (Box 276)
          Catalog # DSKO 135; A-side Matrix # STDSKO36043-1
        - Gem - Sweet temptation, 1983; SR-14459; Gem (Box 276)
          Catalog # DJA-1116; A-side Matrix # DJ-A-1116
          Streetking Records
        - Genaside II - New life 4 the hunted (Disc one), 1996; SR-14460; Genaside II (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14461; SR-14462. Triple album.
          Catalog # TRU LP 14; A-side Matrix # TRULP14-A1
          Internal
        - Genaside II - New life 4 the hunted (Disc two), 1996; SR-14461; Genaside II (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14460; SR-14462. Triple album.
          Catalog # TRU LP 14; A-side Matrix # TRULP14-C1
        - Genaside II - New life 4 the hunted (Disc three), 1996; SR-14462; Genaside II (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14460; SR-14461. Triple album.
          Catalog # TRU LP 14; A-side Matrix # TRULP14-E1
        - Gene Loves Jezebel - Bruises, 1983; SR-14463; Gene Loves Jezebel (Box 276)
          Catalog # SIT 24T; A-side Matrix # SIT 24T-A1
          Situation Two
        - General - Samba hey, 1997; SR-14464; General (Box 276)
          Catalog # 2337-1RLDJ; A-side Matrix # 2337-1-RLDJ-1-A
          Ariola Dance
          Coral Gables, Florida
        - General - Muévelo, 1991; SR-14465; General (Box 276)
          Catalog # 2854-1-RLD; A-side Matrix # 2854-1-RLD-A
          RCA International
        - General - Son bow, SR-14466; General (Box 276)
          Catalog # NCD-001; A-side Matrix # NC-001-A
          New Creations
        - General Caine - Don't stop; For lovers only, 1982; SR-14467; General Caine (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14468. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 4Z9 03358; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-03358-3AE
          Tabu Records
        - General Caine - Don't stop; For lovers only, 1982; SR-14468; General Caine (Box 276)
          In same jacket as # SR-14467. Multiple copies.
        - General Caine - Bomb body, 1983; SR-14469; General Caine (Box 276)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04063; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04063-3AA
        - General Caine - Dangerous, 1983; SR-14470; General Caine (Box 276)
          Catalog # FZ 38863; A-side Matrix # PAL-38863-1E
        - General Caine - Ooh, aah, 1983; SR-14471; General Caine (Box 277)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04251; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04251-3 AB
        - General Caine - Girls; Baseball, 1982; SR-14472; General Caine (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14473. Multiple copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # AS 1492; A-side Matrix # XSS-169025-1A
        - General Caine - Girls; Baseball, 1982; SR-14473; General Caine (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14472. Multiple copies.
        - General Chow - Annihilating groove thing, 1988; SR-14474; General Chow (Box 277)
          Catalog # SR 12003; A-side Matrix # SR-120003-A
          Stolen Records
        - General Kane - Crack killed applejack, 1986; SR-14475; General Kane (Box 277)
          Catalog # PR-192; A-side Matrix # PR-192-67607/67609
          Gordy
        - General Kane - Crack killed applejack, 1986; SR-14476; General Kane (Box 277)
        - General Kane - Girl pulled the dog, 1987; SR-14477; General Kane (Box 277)
          Catalog # 4588 MG; A-side Matrix # 4588MG-F1-67866-67867-15A
        - General Public - I'll take you there, 1994; SR-14478; General Public (Box 277)
          Catalog # 49 77460; A-side Matrix # XSS77460A-1A
        - General, Ricky - Skettle combo, SR-14479; General, Ricky (Box 277)
          Catalog # HI-5001; A-side Matrix # HI-5001-A-RE1
          Hot Ice Records
        - General, Ricky - Skettle combo, SR-14480; General, Ricky (Box 277)
        - General, Ricky - Skettle combo, SR-14481; General, Ricky (Box 277)
        - Genesis - Tonight, tonight, tonight (remix long version), 1987; SR-14482; Genesis (Box 277)
          Catalog # 0-86722; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51362-50017-2
        - Genetix - UFO; Values, 1999; SR-14483; Genetix (Box 277)
          Catalog # SHURE 3; A-side Matrix # SHURE 3-A
          Shure Recordings
        - Gengo, Kate - Tell me, 1988; SR-14484; Gengo, Kate (Box 277)
          Catalog # 4Z9 07819; A-side Matrix # 4Z9 07819-3-AA
          CBS Associated Records
        - Genius - Pass the bone, 1994; SR-14485; Genius (Box 277)
          Catalog # CCPRO 2045; A-side Matrix # CC-PRO-2045-A
          Cold Chillin'
        - Genlog - More music, 1998; SR-14486; Genlog (Box 277)
          Annoted.
          Catalog # 4014235 23720; A-side Matrix # LS 011-A1
          Low Spirit Recordings
        - Genovese - F**k y'all, 2001; SR-14487; Genovese (Box 277)
          Catalog # UNIR 20364-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20364-1A
          Universal Records
        - Genovese - My life, 2000; SR-14488; Genovese (Box 277)
          Catalog # UNIR-20069-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20069-1-A
        - Genovese - F**k y'all, 2001; SR-14489; Genovese (Box 277)
        - Genovese - My life, 2000; SR-14490; Genovese (Box 277)
        - Genuine - Crack busting mission, 1986; SR-14491; Genuine (Box 277)
          Catalog # EM-994; A-side Matrix # EM-944-ARE
          Edwin Matos Media Inc (EMM)
        - Genuine Parts - Show me what to do, 1988; SR-14492; Genuine Parts (Box 277)
          Catalog # DMD 1230; A-side Matrix # STDM-55704-55705-1
        - Genuine Parts - Did it feel like love, 1986; SR-14493; Genuine Parts (Box 277)
          Catalog # DMD 1013; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51156-51155-1
        - Geo & Ricochet - Don't sleep!; Lil sum' em - sum' em, 1994; SR-14494; Geo & Ricochet (Box 277)
          Catalog # GO 6789; A-side Matrix # GO-6789-A
          Gifted Records
        - George, Sophia - For everyone, 1989; SR-14495; George, Sophia (Box 277)
          Catalog # PW 7411; A-side Matrix # PW-7411-A
          Pow Wow Records
        - George, Sophia - Girlie girlie; Girl rush, 1985; SR-14496; George, Sophia; Winner All Stars (Box 277)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # VPRD 244-1
          Winner
          Jamaica
        - George, Sophia - Girlie girlie, 1986; SR-14497; George, Sophia (Box 277)
          Catalog # 0-20490; A-side Matrix # 0 20490 A SH1
          Sire
        - Georgie Porgie - Everybody must party (Disc one), 1995; SR-14498; Georgie Porgie (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14499. Double album.
          Catalog # VIB028; A-side Matrix # VIB028A
          Vibe Music
        - Georgie Porgie - Everybody must party (Disc two), 1995; SR-14499; Georgie Porgie (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14498. Double album.
          Catalog # VIB028; A-side Matrix # VIB028C
        - Georgio - Bedrock, 1987; SR-14500; Georgio (Box 277)
          Catalog # 4603MG; A-side Matrix # PR224A-67960-15A
        - Georgio - I don't want 2 be alone, 1988; SR-14501; Georgio (Box 277)
          Catalog # L33-17688; A-side Matrix # MCA-8420-FDS-1
        - Georgio - Rollin, 1991; SR-14502; Georgio (Box 277)
          Catalog # RDCD62031-1; A-side Matrix # 62031-1-C-1S
          RCA
        - Georgio - Lover's lane, 1987; SR-14503; Georgio (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14504. Different discs.
          Catalog # 4592MG; A-side Matrix # 4592MGA6787067871-15A
        - Georgio - Lover's lane, 1987; SR-14504; Georgio (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14503. Different discs.
          Catalog # 4592MG; A-side Matrix # 4592MGRE1A-67916167870
        - Georgio - Romantic love, 1989; SR-14505; Georgio (Box 277)
          Catalog # MOT-4633; A-side Matrix # MOT 8830 FDS-1
        - Geraldine - Don't fight the feeling, 1972; SR-14506; Geraldine (Box 277)
          Catalog # LD 1001; A-side Matrix # ST-LD-722511B
          Little David Records
        - German, Robert - Marlboro man, 2006; SR-14507; German, Robert (Box 277)
          Catalog # OOTB02; A-side Matrix # OVT-002-A
          Out Of The Blue
        - Gertner, Scott - Queen of the boulevard, 1988; SR-14508; Gertner, Scott (Box 277)
          Catalog # 4Z9 08123; A-side Matrix # XSS08123A-1A
        - Gertner, Scott - Queen of the boulevard, 1988; SR-14509; Gertner, Scott (Box 277)
        - Gertner, Scott - Queen of the boulevard, 1988; SR-14510; Gertner, Scott (Box 277)
        - Get Fresh Girls - Trickin', 1991; SR-14511; Get Fresh Girls (Box 277)
          Catalog # BA-1001; A-side Matrix # BA-1001-A-C1
          Breakaway Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Get It Boyz - Shake yo booty (boom), 1994; SR-14512; Get It Boyz (Box 277)
          Catalog # PD-115; A-side Matrix # PD-115-A
          Pandisc
          Miami Beach, Florida
        - Get Wet - Get wet, 1981; SR-14513; Get Wet (Box 277)
          Catalog # FW 37134; A-side Matrix # FW AL 37134 1B
          The Boardwalk Entertainment Co
        - Geto Boys - Uncut dope, 1992; SR-14514; Geto Boys (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14515. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 6640; A-side Matrix # S-27059
          Rap-A-Lot Records
        - Geto Boys - Uncut dope, 1992; SR-14515; Geto Boys (Box 277)
          In same jacket as # SR-14514. Multiple copies.
        - Geto Boys - Hot club wax, 1993; SR-14516; Geto Boys (Box 277)
          Catalog # SPRO 6660; A-side Matrix # SPRO- 6660A-Z1
        - Geto Boys - Gangsta (put me down), 1998; SR-14517; Geto Boys (Box 277)
          Catalog # 7087 6 13647 1 2; A-side Matrix # SPRO-72438-13647-1-2-A
          Houston, Texas
        - Geto Boys - Club wax, 1996; SR-14518; Geto Boys (Box 277)
          Catalog # SPRO 11512; A-side Matrix # V1-41555-A
        - Geto Boys - Uncut dope, 1992; SR-14519; Geto Boys (Box 277)
        - Geyer, Renée - It's a man's man's world, 1983; SR-14520; Geyer, Renée (Box 277)
          Catalog # L-37980; A-side Matrix # SMX60323
          Australia
        - Geza X - You goddam kids!, 1981; SR-14521; Geza X (Box 277)
          Catalog # YGK AB; A-side Matrix # YGK A
          Final Gear Records
        - GF And Friends - Body language; Ride on bones, 1977; SR-14522; GF And Friends; Funny Bone (Box 277)
          Catalog # D12-3; A-side Matrix # Q12-A-4383
          Monument
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Ghetto Boys - Be down, 1988; SR-14523; Ghetto Boys (Box 277)
          Catalog # RAP-50; A-side Matrix # RAP 50-A
        - Ghetto Funk - Doing my thing, 2000; SR-14524; Ghetto Funk (Box 278)
          Catalog # GFUNK-001; A-side Matrix # GFUNK-001-A-1
          G-Funk Records
        - Ghetto Mafia - On da grind (remix); In Decatur (remix), 1999; SR-14525; Ghetto Mafia (Box 278)
          Catalog # PRO-4062-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4602-1A
          Fully Loaded Records
        - Ghetto Mafia - In Decatur; Ghetto Mafia, 1998; SR-14526; Ghetto Mafia (Box 278)
          Catalog # PRO-4061; A-side Matrix # PRO-4061-A
        - Ghetto People - Fever, 1997; SR-14527; Ghetto People; L-Viz (Box 278)
          Catalog # DAN 664288 6; A-side Matrix # 1c 004c88 c0 1A1
          Dance Pool
          The Netherlands
        - Ghetto People - In the ghetto, 1996; SR-14528; Ghetto People; L-Viz (Box 278)
          Catalog # DAN 663676 6; A-side Matrix # 12 663676 20 1A1
        - Ghetto Philharmonic - Hip-hop be-bop, 1994; SR-14529; Ghetto Philharmonic (Box 278)
          Catalog # TUF LP 0607; A-side Matrix # TUF LP 0607 A
          Tuff City
        - Ghetto Starz - Let it be known; Da fam, 1998; SR-14530; Ghetto Starz; Wayne-O Of The E Bros.; Rocigarson; Bossfam (Box 278)
          Catalog # AV48; A-side Matrix # AV-48-A
          AV8
        - Ghostt - The players anthem, 1998; SR-14531; Ghostt (Box 278)
          Catalog # TH2260; A-side Matrix # TH 2260 A
          Thump Street Records
          Walnut, California
        - Ghost, Amanda - Filthy mind (Disc one), 2000; SR-14532; Ghost, Amanda (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14533. Double album.
          Catalog # 0-44855; A-side Matrix # 0-44855-A-SR1
          Kinetic Records
        - Ghost, Amanda - Filthy mind (Disc two), 2000; SR-14533; Ghost, Amanda (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14532. Double album.
          Catalog # 0-44855; A-side Matrix # 0-44855-C
        - Ghost Town DJ's - My boo, 1995; SR-14534; Ghost Town DJ's (Box 278)
          Catalog # 44 78358; A-side Matrix # XSS 78358-A-1B
          So so def
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Tush, 2004; SR-14535; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface; Elliot, Missy (Box 278)
          Catalog # DEFR 16019-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16019-1A-R1
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Tush, 2004; SR-14536; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface; Elliot, Missy (Box 278)
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Tush; Holla, 2004; SR-14537; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface; Elliot, Missy (Box 278)
          Catalog # DEFR 16044-1; A-side Matrix # B0002315-11A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc one), 2004; SR-14538; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14539. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16056-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16056-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc two), 2004; SR-14539; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14538. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16057-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16057-1A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - All that I got is you, 1997; SR-14540; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14541. Different discs.
          Catalog # XPR 3142; A-side Matrix # 31 3142 20 1A1
          Razor Sharp Records
        - Remedy - Seen it all; Everything is real, 1997; SR-14541; Remedy (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14540. Different discs.
          Catalog # FAR 0666; A-side Matrix # FAR-0666-A
          Fifth Angel Recordings
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Save me dear, 2004; SR-14542; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          Catalog # DEFR 16104-1; A-side Matrix # B0002857-11A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc one), 2004; SR-14543; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14544. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc two), 2004; SR-14544; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14543. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Save me dear, 2004; SR-14545; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc one), 2004; SR-14546; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14547. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002169-01; A-side Matrix # B0002169-01-LP1A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - The Pretty Toney album (exclusive album advance) (Disc two), 2004; SR-14547; Ghostface Killah (Rapper); Ghostface (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14546. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002169-01; A-side Matrix # B0002169-01-LP2A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc one), 2006; SR-14548; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14549. Double album.
          Catalog # B0006155-01; A-side Matrix # B0006155-01 LP01-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc two), 2006; SR-14549; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14548. Double album.
          Catalog # B0006155-01; A-side Matrix # B0006155-01 LP02-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Supreme Clientele (Disc one), 2000; SR-14550; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14551. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 69325; A-side Matrix # 63576 AL-2
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Supreme Clientele (Disc two), 2000; SR-14551; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14550. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 69325; A-side Matrix # 63577 AL-2
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Be easy, 2005; SR-14552; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          Catalog # DEFR 16341-1; A-side Matrix # B0005116-11-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Back like that, 2006; SR-14553; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          Catalog # DEFR 16485-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16485-1-A-1
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc one), 2006; SR-14554; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14555. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16506-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16506-1-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc two), 2006; SR-14555; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14554. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16507-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16507-1-A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Back like that, 2006; SR-14556; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Cherchez LaGhost, 2000; SR-14557; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          Catalog # 49 79438; A-side Matrix # XSS 79438 A
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc one), 2006; SR-14558; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14559. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc two), 2006; SR-14559; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14558. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc one), 2006; SR-14560; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14561. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Fishscale (Disc two), 2006; SR-14561; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          In same jacket as # SR-14560. Double album.
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - Be easy, 2005; SR-14562; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
        - Ghostface Killah (Rapper) - CherChez LaGhost, 2000; SR-14563; Ghostface Killah (Rapper) (Box 278)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # CERCHEZ LAGHOST
        - Giant Steps - Into you, 1988; SR-14564; Giant Steps (Box 278)